scubaocity.com 2009-01-30

# 

* * *

**PRIVACY STATEMENT **

Our Commitment to You: Aquatic Diver, Inc, d/b/a Scubaocity.com (“Scubaocity,” "Company," "we," "our," or "us") is dedicated to establishing trust with you, our customer, and to protecting your privacy, as well as the privacy of your customers whom use our services. All personal identifying information collected by us will be used for the sole purpose of maintaining our relationship with you and help you maintain your relationship with your customers. Our contact information is as follows:

    Aquatic Diver, Inc d/b/a Scubaocity

    158 Coconut Row

   Tavernier, FL 33070

  Office: 970-455-4311

    info@scubaocity.com  

**Skype Us Now**

When you sign up for services with Scubaocity or your customer makes a purchase on your website (using our technology), we will ask for contact and payment information. The contact information includes name, address, phone number and email address. Payment information typically includes a credit card number and information necessary to conduct a credit card transaction for the services purchased on our website or using our technology.

The mission of Scubaocity.com is to help make the Internet experience wonderful for its customers. The utmost respect, protection and regard for personally identifying information represent a key component of this mission. Therefore, this Privacy Statement forms a contract between Aquatic Diver, Inc and your organization, and therefore Scubaocity (and its related companies) cannot use, resell or make available personally identifying information for any organization except yours or as otherwise explicitly agreed to by the customer.

For the rest of this Privacy Statement, the words “we,” “our,” or “Scubaocity” shall mean Scubaocity.com, Aquatic Diver, Inc. and any/all of its vendors and third-party relationships.

We collect traffic patterns and information from our web servers, but this information is not combined or used with or in conjunction with personally identifiable information.

We may use cookies or session variables, as necessary, to maintain sessions with our servers on a transaction basis. However, we never use cookies or session variables to track movement outside our web servers or tie your movement to the personally identifying information we maintain.

**What Do We Use Personally Identifying Information For?**

We only use personally identifying information to conduct, facilitate or in furtherance of a transaction. For example, we use personally identifying information to charge a credit card for services. We will also send transactional notices to a purchaser and their gift recipient(s), including reminders that a service or gift certificate has not yet been redeemed.

We may, only to support a particular transaction, release your personally identifying information to a third-party, such as a credit card processor, Delivery Company, or other third-party as would be necessary to complete the transaction with us. If we do this, rest assured that we would only release the minimal information necessary to process the relevant transaction.

If a customer allows us (i.e. by “opt in” when they sign up or register with us), we may send polite marketing messages, such as reminders of upcoming holidays or gift giving ideas.

We may aggregate limited demographic information, purchasing behaviors or web traffic patterns. This information will not be tied or traceable to any personally identifying information.

**What We Do NOT Use Personally Identifying Information For?**

We will never sell, intentionally release or otherwise make available personally identifying information to third parties that are not required for a specific transaction that is requested, unless otherwise compelled by law or court order.

**How Do We Protect Your Personally Identifying Information?**

We protect personally identifying information both online and offline. Online, account information is protected by the leading industry standard method of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption. All credit card information is encoded and protected using multiple layers of network security, including firewall protection. Offline, personally identifying information is also protected in our offices. Our employees are well informed about our privacy practices, and access to customer information is restricted to what is necessary to perform their specific tasks. Moreover, we notify our employees of any changes to our Privacy Statement and corresponding requirements, and we possess polices and procedures to handle privacy complaints and security threats or breaches.

**How Are Updates to this Privacy Statement Made?**

You should check this website frequently for changes, and we encourage you to contact us with any questions you have about the changes or any of our policies. Rest assured that, without your express consent, we will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of your personally identifying information.
